Urgent update. The Israeli occupation forces are planning a new military operation here in Gaza.
I'm here in Gaza City with a few very important updates. Netanyahu just left the U.S. for two
main reasons. One, to sign on to become an official member of the Board of Peace, the U.S.-Israeli
plan, the ethnic cleansing, genocide, and illegal occupation of Gaza. And two, to get U.S. approval
to start a new military operation as Gazans prepare for Ramadan. This is not coincidental.
They've already started military operations in Jabalia, destroying buildings, shooting at Gazans
to continue to forcibly displace them as they illegally occupy over 63% of the Gaza Strip.
And another very important fact, there are no more Israeli hostages. So the IOF literally plans
to exterminate, eliminate, and continue the genocide and ethnic cleansing of Gazans. And now they have
nothing to stop them. They can indiscriminately attack. And they're claiming that this is to
disarm the resistance. But what we have to remember is that Palestinians have a right
to resist their illegal occupation. The Israelis will not be doing this alone. They will begin
to use the International Stabilization Forces, a group of different militaries that have signed
on to the Board of Peace and agreed to help the illegal Israeli occupation. 8,000 Indonesian
troops are on their way to Gaza. Not to save the people that are being genocided, the indigenous
Palestinians. But to help and coordinate with the Israeli occupation forces, this International
Stabilization Force could reach 20,000 international troops. To get an idea of what this new military
occupation could look like, just keep in mind that for the last four months, the Israelis have violated
the ceasefire over 1,600 times, injured over 1,500 Palestinians, and massacred and killed over 573
Ghazans during the so-called ceasefire, which is just propaganda to get the media and to stop
people from talking about Gaza. Less than 85 percent of media outlets are even talking about what's
happening right now, which makes it even more important to continue to share what is happening.
As all of this is happening, the Israeli occupation forces continue to build illegal settlements in the
West Bank. The Knesset is in the process of approving a new law that would allow them to execute Palestinian
hostages. Over 9,000 Palestinians are currently being held illegally, tortured, mutilated, killed,
all while the Israelis continue to steal organs from Palestinians. And all of this will continue to
happen using Venezuelan oil to fuel their genocide. Not because Venezuela is sending oil, but because the
U.S., with the help of the Zionists to use Borinquen as a launch pad, attacked the sovereignty of
Venezuela, kidnapped President Nicolas Maduro and the first combatant Celia Flores. If the oil was still
under the sovereign control of Venezuela, that oil would have been going to Cuba to help them combat
the illegal sanctions that are taking place. It's all connected and we have to continue tangible actions
to break diplomatic ties, enforce an arms embargo, and to get the Zionists out of the Gaza Strip because if we
don't, this next phase of the genocide could be the final phase, the end of the Gaza Strip. And what we
have to continue to remind ourselves of is that what we allow to happen in Gaza will begin to become
the reality everywhere else in the world. It will be the new norm and we cannot normalize the genocide
happening here in Gaza, Palestine, in Congo, or Sudan. Now is the time for tangible actions to end the
genocide before it ends all of us.